[
    {
        "category": "figure",
        "question" : "un",
        "answer" : "one"
    },
    {
        "category": "figure",
        "question" : "deux",
        "answer" : "two"
    },
    {
        "category": "figure",
        "question" : "trois",
        "answer" : "three"
    },
    {
        "category": "figure",
        "question" : "quatre",
        "answer" : "four"
    },
    {
        "category": "figure",
        "question" : "cinq",
        "answer" : "five"
    },
    {
        "category": "figure",
        "question" : "six",
        "answer" : "six"
    },
    {
        "category": "figure",
        "question" : "sept",
        "answer" : "seven"
    },
    {
        "category": "figure",
        "question" : "huit",
        "answer" : "eight"
    },
    {
        "category": "figure",
        "question" : "neuf",
        "answer" : "nine"
    },
    {
        "category": "figure",
        "question" : "dix",
        "answer" : "ten"
    }
]